Adams Morgan Better Neighborhood Conference/Hollyday House
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Adams Morgan Better Neighborhood Conference Records/Hollyday House Papers
1930-1962
DC Public Library, Special Collections
6 linear feet; 11 boxes
018
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Independent Study, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood Conference, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - West Central, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Preliminary steps to prepare for Supreme Court decision re desegregation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Zoning, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Urban renewal, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Public schools, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Relationships between AMBNC Project 314 and Hollyday House, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Businessmen organization, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Demonstration Project 314, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Demonstration Project/Clippings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and Background or purpose, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter Bulletin, 1956-62 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Finances, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Community activities, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Christmas baskets for needy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with D.C. Commissioners, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Recreation Department, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Membership lists, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ministers and churches, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and Steering Committee reports, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Planning Committee I, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hollyday House - Incorporation papers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hollyday House - Dedication, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hollyday House - Guy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hollyday House - Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hollyday House - By-laws, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hollyday House - Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hollyday House - Purposes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hollyday House - History, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hollyday House - Board of Directors, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hollyday House - Committees, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hollyday House - Membership, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hollyday House - Executive Director reports, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hollyday House - Advisory board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hollyday House - Staff, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hollyday House - Annual meetings, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hollyday House - Financial Treasurer reports, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hollyday House - Program Planning Committee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Hollyday House - Revolving loan fund, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Hollyday House - Publicity and advertising, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Hollyday House - Newsletters, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hollyday House - General activities, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hollyday House - Head Start, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hollyday House - Drill Team, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Hollyday House - Summer Program/Fresh Air Programs, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hollyday House - Special Activities, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hollyday House - Financial tax-exempt status, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hollyday House - Fund raising events, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hollyday House - U.G.F., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hollyday House - Fund raising - Sears Roebuck, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hollyday House - Fund raising - Meyer, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hollyday House - Fund raising - Whitney, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hollyday House - Fund raising - Health and Welfare Council, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hollyday House - Fund raising - Financial treasurer reports, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hollyday House - Rehabilitation, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hollyday House - Church of the Brethren, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hollyday House - AMBNC Merger, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hollyday House - AMBNC Block groups, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hollyday House - Photographs - A-M, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hollyday House - Photographs - General, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hollyday House - Photographs - General, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hollyday House - Photographs - General, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hollyday House - Photographs - Miscellaneous - general, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Hollyday House - Annual Meetings, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hollyday House - Minutes - Board of Directors, 1957-1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hollyday House - Minutes - Board of Directors, 1957-1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hollyday House - Minutes - Board of Directors, 1957-1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Hollyday House - Minutes - Board of Directors, 1957-1966 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - Singing engagements, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - Conference funds, 7/1957-2/1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - Songs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - Logistics-Transportation, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - General Information, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hollyday House Chorus - List of singers, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Barney House, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Urban Peace Corps, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Studies and reports, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous papers (newsletters, etc.), Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)